funfastgame.com 2014-06-20

# FUNFASTGAME PRIVACY POLICY | Free Online Games

FunFastGame is committed to providing an entertaining, fun and educational service. FunFastGame.com is a property of FunFastGame Limited “FunFastGame”. FunFastGame respects the privacy concerns of visitors to FunFastGame.com. FunFastGame does not target its website or services to under 13 year olds, but does take measures to help protect those that happen to be under 13. We take measures to help children protect their privacy while online. For example, we do not ask children to disclose more personal information than is necessary for them to participate in a particular activity.

Information we collect  
We may log IP addresses and/or drop cookies to prevent abuse of our website and/or to enhance services. Email addresses of under 13 year olds are not stored. They are encrypted into an unrecoverable format using a one way hash.

How we use the information  
We have an internal notification system to communicate with under 13 players and do not send them emails. We do not retain any personal information beyond the time it is needed. We may use information to ensure that users are compliance with our terms. Over 13′s may authorize and receive email notifications related to FunFastGame services. FunFastGame Limited may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with FunFastGame’s property, visitors, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

We may sometimes use non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site, to personalize our visitors’ experience or to offer products, programs, and services. We may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer products, programs, or services.

Collection of Information and Third-Party Sites and Sponsors  
Our site may place a small file, called a cookie, on your hard drive to provide you with a better website. A cookie does not, in any way, give us access to your computer or to any personally identifiable information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. It only helps us analyze web traffic or lets web applications respond to you as an individual.

Our authorized third-party advertisers in the course of serving ads to you, may also place cookies on your browser or use tracking technology to collect information. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser?s settings section.

Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a DART cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google?s use of cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Information that is reasonably necessary  
FunFastGame does not require under 13′s to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity as a condition of participation.

Security  
We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

Parental Review  
To protect your child’s privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting you access to the personal information that we collect and maintain about your child.

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
This Privacy Policy is part of the FunFastGame main Terms and Conditions which you agree to by accessing the FunFastGame.com webstie and/or services. You agree that FunFastGame Limited may change this Privacy Policy and the main FunFastGame Terms and Conditions at any time. Our current Privacy Policy will be posted here: http://www.FunFastGame.com/?info=privacy which is part of our Terms and Conditions posted here: http://www.FunFastGame.com/?info=tos

Internet Safety  
FunFastGame recommends that Parents take time to communicate and educate their children about Internet Safety.

## Play all best free online games on the net

Known worldwide as a platform that provides cool **games** , funny **games** online, FunFastGame.com delivers mass market appeal globally and the established flash **games** provider experiments with innovation all the time, bringing to its adept users gaming experiences to exceed their expectations. At FunFastGame.com, we create unique and media-rich online **games** that provide **gaming** experiences intricately designed and implemented for the purpose of enhancing **game** visualization as well as interaction. Using dynamic and media-driven applications for the purpose of designing cool games and funny **games** , FunFastGame.com is all about brilliance and we seek nothing but critical reception when we launch games. You have to be insane not to like FunFastGame.com and it's arcade of free online games.
